

VICTOR SVETAILO

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT













CONTACT



Phone

+7 962 007 05 55



Fmail

victorsvetailo@gmail.com



Address

Turkey Antalya 07040



EDUCATION

 $(\mathbf{2})$ IT-Incubator 2022



Frontend developer.

(React/Redux/TypeScript)

Freelancer for life link \odot 2020 - 2021





Creating websites Course. HTML, CSS (SCSS), JS

WAY UP & Gavrilov \odot



HTML - CSS, Wordpress Bootstrap Course.



LANGUAGE

Native

Pre-Intermediate English in progress

Temel 2 Turkish



ABOUT ME

Hello everyone. I'm Front-End developer with experience and good knowledge in creating SPA using React, Redux, Typescript, JS, HTML, and CSS. Almost every day I improve my skills. I'm planning to study Node.is because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. I would like to find a job in a creative company with up-to-date tasks and a collaborative team! Open for your suggestions!



MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- JavaScript / TypeScriptUnitTest / Jest / TDD

React

- StoryBook / Postman
- Redux / Redux-Toolkit
- Formik / Redux Form
- Rest API / Axios
- Ant Design / Material UI
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS
- Git/GitHub



WORK EXPERIENCE

() EnglishShow @ link

Online IT School 2021 - 2022

KodKodych A link



Mentor. HR. Development of programming courses.

December 2021 - present day

Full time.

Stack: HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS, JavaScript, React, Scratch

TRAINING CARDS. GitHub link



November 2022 - present day

Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Formik, Material-UI. Using TypeScript for better code control, ESLint, Prettier for the best code style. Organizing correct app arcitecture. Team development: bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

TODO LIST GitHub link



July 2022 - November 2022

Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Material-UI. Using TypeScript for better code control. Covering code with unit tests, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

SOCIAL NETWORK GitHub link



2020 - 2022

February 2022 - September 2022

Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Redux-form, Ant Design, Reselect. Using TypeScript for better code control, ESLint, Prettier for the best code style. Creating unit tests, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying. Organizing correct app arcitecture.

() HelloWorld iink Online IT School

MENTOR. TEACHER OF PROGRAMMING COURSES

December 2020 - January 2022 Full time.

Stack: HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS, JavaScript, Lua, Scratch

(2016 - 2020) Own business in the field of online stores.